<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blog on Crystal Wake (MuxLuxx)</title>
    <link>https://muxluxx.github.io/categories/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in blog on Crystal Wake (MuxLuxx)</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://muxluxx.github.io/categories/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DEFCON 31 &#43; BlackHat 2023</title>
      <link>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2023-10-12-defcon-31/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2023-10-12-defcon-31/</guid>
      <description>Defcon 31 &amp;amp; BlackHat USA 2023 with Friends Overview This year was the first year I was able to come back and see my friends at Defcon &amp;amp; Black Hat. The experience was wonderful! I got to meet people that I have been talking to for years online but never met. One of those wonderful people was Admiral! He has been my mentor since 2020 when I first joined the DC801 Defcon Group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mux makes live changes</title>
      <link>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2022-06-01-learning-more/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2022-06-01-learning-more/</guid>
      <description>Mux&amp;rsquo;s changes and what to do next? Recently, I have been gone for quite a while and the reason for this was due to my streaming schedule. I also for some time ran a shop on Etsy but unfortunately had to close down due to the amount it was costing me to run this. I had to pay an additional closing cost along with this. I have had to close shop eventhough I would have perferred not to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I left and where I have been...</title>
      <link>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2022-01-18-back_again/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2022-01-18-back_again/</guid>
      <description>Where have I been? I have been gone for quite a bit and I decided to post of where I have been and why I have been gone recently. The reason for me being gone is depressingly enough is depression. I have struggled with it in the past and things I use to find enjoyment in are no longer making me happy. Why is this? I have had people who I was decently close to pass away and I am trying to deal with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Being an adult</title>
      <link>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2021-11-07-re-evaluation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2021-11-07-re-evaluation/</guid>
      <description>Lately, I have been looking into what is important and what I need to do. Honestly, one of the most important things I learned recently is what I want in my life and how to achieve it. For me, recently I have been getting into body building and fitness due to my fears of being overweight. I started to have weight issues when I was young becuase I loved sweets and thought I could eat anything.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s talk about Progress</title>
      <link>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2021-11-03-progress_with_mux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2021-11-03-progress_with_mux/</guid>
      <description>Progress is key! Hope you all are having a wonderful fall so far and are enjoying the wonderful weather!
I want some cinnamon iced coffee or horchata. Please horchata&amp;hellip;
Back on topic, progress is important and learning is part of that process. Recently I have been looking over my life to re-evaluate a couple of areas that I can improve. A couple of these areas are as follows -
Health/Fitness IT Knowledge Learning to save money These areas are where I fall flat on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween from Mux</title>
      <link>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2021-10-31-happy_halloween/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2021-10-31-happy_halloween/</guid>
      <description>Happy Halloween my Devs, Hackers, IT and Admins! Hope you are all having a spooky night and get lots of candy, scares and much more.
Putting on the witch hat tonight and watching Resident Evil. I love me a good pyramid head!
But most importantly, I thought it would be great to show some of the wonderful twitter posts about all the wonderful things IT Twitter has come out with. Below are some of my personal favorites!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bandit Challenge</title>
      <link>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2021-10-30-bandit_challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2021-10-30-bandit_challenges/</guid>
      <description>The bandit challenge has been one of the most interesting challenges to date for me. I am really new into tech and need to catch up with my friends. As a whole, I think this challenge has proven two things.
I have no idea how to use linux. I am very far behind my friends in IT. One of my biggest regrets in IT, is not taking the time to look into tech.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixing Websites</title>
      <link>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2021-10-28-fixing_things/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2021-10-28-fixing_things/</guid>
      <description>Blog about fixing things&amp;hellip; Fixing things can be hard especially when you are starting out for the first time. Sometimes you need a helpful goose (admiral) to help you out.
Sometimes you are fine and then something happens and you mess up. If you can&amp;rsquo;t figure it out, ask around and get some help. Usually for me that is a goose that flies around on my screen and honks at me when I need to look at something.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2021-10-27-first_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2021-10-27-first_post/</guid>
      <description>What even is Hugo? It seems it is a static site generator. Hugo is like bread to website with butter added on the plate. Morally wrong but it works.
Butter dog, puts butter on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning New Things</title>
      <link>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2021-10-27-learning_new/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://muxluxx.github.io/blog/2021-10-27-learning_new/</guid>
      <description>What even are websites and how to build a post? I have been learning alot from my friends at DC801. Recently, I have been working on a special projec t that I have been working with them on. I can&amp;rsquo;t say much but involves a certain little mage. Hope you all will like it and try to keep an eye on all the different things on DC801 and my twitter for more information as well!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
